A Guide to the Institute of International Education records, Alumni and Historical Files, RG 1 FA1289
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Historical Files, 3
  - Stephen Duggan Trip to Europe with Dr. Monroe Vacation and Canada Trip 1923 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 2)
  - Stephen Duggan Phillipines Educationa Commission Trip to Far East, Russia, Near East, Europe 1924-1925 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 2)
  - Stephen Duggan Personal File Incl. Correspondence with Nicholas Murray Butler re Institute, General Correspondence 1921-1934 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Correspondence with Dr. Butler re Status and Needs of the Institute, Reports on Institute Activities, Reports on Administration of Funds 1926 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan General Correspondence re IIE Various Proposals, Activities, Budgets 1927 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Reorganization of the Institute Correspondence re The Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial Trust 1928 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan European Trip 1928 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan CCNY Testimonial Dinner 1928 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 18)
  - General Re Great Silver Cross of Merit Awarded to Dr. Duggan 1928 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Re Chapter in Textbook on International Relations 1924 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan General Correspondence re Articles 1929 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan General Correspondence Re Speeches and Articles 1929 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Articles Background of the Chinese Chaos Factors in the Chinese Situation 1929 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Re "Cultural Relations Between the Orient and the Occident" 1929 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Re Aricle on Cultural Relations between the Orient and Occident 1929-1930 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Correspondence Re Travels and Visits (Europe, Washington, Chicago) 1930 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan General Correspondence Re Books and Articles 1930 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Re Article on China 1930 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Correspondence RE Books and Article "Good Bye, England" 1930 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 18)
  - General Reports on visits to Unversities by Prof. Duggan 1930 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Russia Radio Address 1930 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 2)
  - Stephen Duggan Personal Correspondence 1931 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Visit to South America General Correspondence Copies of Lectures 1931 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen P. Duggan American-Russian Institute 1933 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 10)
  - Stephen Duggan The Two Americas Drafts and Corrections 1934 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 4)
  - Stephen Duggan Correspondence RE The Two Americas 1934 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 4)
  - Stephen Duggan CBS Radio Broadcasts 1934 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 5)
  - Stephen Duggan Radio Columbia 1934-1935 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 5)
  - Stephen Duggan Russia Famine Reports 1934-1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 11)
  - Stephen Duggan Correspondence Re Russia 1934-1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 11)
  - Stephen Duggan Russia M-Z 1934-1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 11)
  - Stephen Duggan Correspondence Re The Two Americas 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 22), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 10)
  - Stephen Duggan CBS Radio Broadcasts Correspondence A-Z 1935 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 5)
  - Stephen Duggan CBS Radio Broadcasts Correspondence from Listeners 1935 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 5)
  - Stephen Duggan Radio Columbia 1935 231 7-20 (Ree7 5, Side 1, Index 8), Ree7 5, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 5)
  - Stephen Duggan Visits 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 10)
  - Stephen Duggan Western Trip 1936 213 7-2 (Ree7 4, Side 2, Index 22), Ree7 4, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 4)
  - Stephen P. Duggan Books and Articles 1936 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 4)
  - Stephen Duggan Books and Articles 1936 Student Textbook on History of Education 1936 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 4)
  - Stephen Duggan The Two Americas 1936 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 27), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 27 (Reel 5)
  - Stephen Duggan Academic Freedom Dinner 1936 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 28), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 28 (Reel 5)
  - Stephen P. Duggan Correspondence Re Books and Articles 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 21), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 21 (Reel 10)
  - Stephen Duggan U.S. Committee on Educational Reconstruction 1943 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 39), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 39 (Reel 12)
  - Stephen Duggan Correspondence RE Books and Articles 1943-1944 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Iranian Institute 1945 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 15)
  - Stephen Duggan Iranian Institute Financial 1945 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 15)
  - Stephen Duggan RE The Rescue of Science and Learning 1947 (Reel 15, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 15, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 15)
  - Stephen Duggan General Correspondence A-L 1947-1948 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan RE CCNY Dinner 1948 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Correspondence RE Charities and Fund-Raising Organizations Letter of Sympathy Acknowledged 1948-1949 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Correspondence 1949 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 18)
  - General Stephen Duggan Editorial On International Education 1949-1950 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 20), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 20 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Duplicate Material on Books 1949-1950 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 18)
  - Stephen Duggan Manuscripts and Material Used in Writing Report on International Education 1950 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 18)
  - Estonia 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 15)
  - Ethiopia 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 15)
  - Egypt 1938 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 51), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 51 (Reel 10)
  - Egypt 1944 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 13)
  - Egypt - General 1944, 1948 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 39), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 39 (Reel 15)
  - Egypt - General 1948-50 (Reel 15, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 15, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 15)
  - Egypt - General 1950-51 (Reel 20, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 20, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 20)
  - Emergency Committee W. Koetchning - General 1934 and 1944 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 9)
  - Emergency Committee Germany Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced German Scholars 1936 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 9)
  - Germany Emergency Committee 1939 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 10)
  - Emergency Committee General 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 10)
  - Emergency Committee General 1943 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 24), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 24 (Reel 9)
  - Emergency Committee Refugee Scholar Fund Clearance Committee - Minutes 1943 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 9)
  - Emergency Committee Stephen Duggan General Coorespondence RE History of Emergency Committee 1946 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 9)
  - Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced Foreign Scholars General 1946 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 9)
  - English-Speaking Union American Association of University Women - 1919-25 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 2)
  - English-Speaking Union - 1936 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 5)
  - English-Speaking Union - 1937 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 7)
  - English-Speaking Union - 1939 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 9)
  - Historical Documents - Federal Council of Churches 1932 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 4)
  - Stephen Duggan Foreign Policy Association 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 32), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 32 (Reel 12)
  - Foreign Policy Associations 1943 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 40), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 40 (Reel 13)
  - Stephen Duggan Foreign Policy Association 1945 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 28), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 28 (Reel 15)
  - Foreign Policy Associations 1947 (Reel 15, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 15, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 15)
  - Finland - Special Projects - 1939 (Reel 21, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 21, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 21)
  - Finland - 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 29), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 29 (Reel 10)
  - Finland - 1944 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 13)
  - Finland - Finnish Committee - Correspondence - 1949 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 17)
  - Finland - Finnish Committee on Study and Training in the United States - 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 21), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 21 (Reel 19)
  - Finland - 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 24), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 24 (Reel 19)
  - Finland - Selection Committee Correspondence - 1953-54 (Reel 29, Side 1, Index 38), Reel 29, Side 1, Index 38 (Reel 29)
  - Finland - Department of State (IES) Correspondence U.S. Cultural Officer-Helsinki - 1953-54 (Reel 29, Side 1, Index 39), Reel 29, Side 1, Index 39 (Reel 29)
  - Finland - U.S. Olympic Committee Fellowship - 1953-54 (Reel 29, Side 1, Index 37), Reel 29, Side 1, Index 37 (Reel 29)
  - Finland - Selection Committee (Finnish Committee on Study and Training in the U.S.) Correspondence - 1956-57 - 1956 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 33)
  - Finland - Department of State (IES) Correspondence - 1956-57 - 1956 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 33)
  - Finland - Selection Committee (Finnish Committee on Study and Training in the U.S.) Correspondence - 1957-58 - 1957 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 30)
  - Finland - Department of State (IES) Correspondence - 1957-58 - 1957 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 30)
  - Finland - Committee on Study and Training in the United States - Itinerary for Miss Maija Arola - 1960 (Reel 27, Side 27, Index 27), Reel 27, Side 27, Index 27 (Reel 27)
  - France - Assistants, Correspondence, Records of Candidaates - 1921-24 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 2)
  - France - Engineers - 1922-25 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 2)
  - France - Art Scholarship Correspondence - 1929 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 3)
  - France - Art Scholarships - 1930 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 3)
  - France - U.S. Cite Universitaire - 1930 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 3)
  - France - 1931 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 3)
  - Special Projects - France - 1932 - A-G (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 21), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 21 (Reel 8)
  - France - U.S. Cite Universitaire - 1932 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 3)
  - France - 1933 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 4)
  - France - A-Z - 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 4)
  - France - Art - 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 35), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 35 (Reel 4)
  - France - Desclos - 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 36), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 36 (Reel 4)
  - France - Wooley Fellowships - 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 37), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 37 (Reel 4)
  - France - General - 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 11)
  - France - U.S. Cite Universitaire - 1934 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 5)
  - France - Art School - 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 11)
  - France - Desclos - 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 20), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 20 (Reel 11)
  - France - Wooley Fellowships - 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 21), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 21 (Reel 11)
  - France - U.S. Cite Universitaire - 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 10)
  - Special Projects - France - Plan A - 1935 (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 30), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 30 (Reel 8)
  - France - Assistant Successful - 1932-33 - 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 32), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 32 (Reel 10)
  - France - Re Visit of 11 American Men (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 48), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 48 (Reel 11)
  - France - Assistantships - General - 1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 11)
  - France - Institute of Art and Archaeology - 1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 11)
  - France - Desclos - 1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 11)
  - France - Wooley Scholarships Art - 1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 11)
  - Special Projects -France - 1936 - Professor Charles Cestre (Reel 8, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 8, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 8)
  - Special Projects - France - Plan A - M. Etienne Dennery - 1936 (Reel 8, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 8, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 8)
  - Special Projects - France - Plan B - Professor Lucien Wolff - 1936 (Reel 8, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 8, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 8)
  - France - General - 1936 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 24), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 24 (Reel 7)
  - France - Franco-American Student Exchange Art Fellowships, General - 1936 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 7)
  - France - U.S. Cite Universitaire - 1936 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 24), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 24 (Reel 5)
  - France - Assistant General - 1936 (Reel 5, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 5, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 5)
  - France - Desclos - 1936 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 7)
  - France - Wooley Scholarships - 1936 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 30), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 30 (Reel 7)
  - France - United States Cite Universitaire - 1937 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 7)
  - France - United States Cite Universitaire - 1938 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 43), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 43 (Reel 7)
  - Special Projects - France - 1938 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 9)
  - Special Projects - France - 1938 (Reel 9, Side 4, Index 4), Reel 9, Side 4, Index 4 (Reel 9)
  - France - Special Projects - A-Z - 1938-39 (Reel 21, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 21, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 21)
  - France - United States Cite Universitaire - 1939 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 9)
  - France - Wooley Scholarships - 1939 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 9)
  - France - General - 1940 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 9)
  - France - Scholars - A-M - 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 10)
  - France - Scholars - N-Z - 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 27), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 27 (Reel 10)
  - France - Refugee - 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 10)
  - France - Fellowships for French - Copies for French-to Digeon - 1940-41 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 6)
  - France - 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 12)
  - France - Refugee Micheline Pohl - 1944-45 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 16)
  - France - French Cultural Service Re Student Exchange - 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 15)
  - France - French Cultural Service - 1947 (Reel 15, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 15, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 15)
  - France - French Cultural Service - 1947 (Reel 15, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 15, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 15)
  - France - Student Exchange Annual Letters - 1947-54 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 33)
  - France - Wooley Scholarship - History Correspondence - 1947-54 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 29)
  - France - Franco-American Student Exchange Early Post-War Correspondence - 1948-50 (Reel 29, Side 1, Index 40), Reel 29, Side 1, Index 40 (Reel 29)
  - France - Anita Lauve - Cultural Attache - 1949 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 17)
  - France - French Cultural Services Correspondence - 1949-50 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 19)
  - France - U.S. Advisory Committee on Franco-American Exchange - 1949-50 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 19)
  - France - Selection Committee - Office National - 1949-50 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 44), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 44 (Reel 19)
  - France - Travel Grant Appointees - 1949-50 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 19)
  - France - Master List of Exchange Students - 1949-50 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 19)
  - France - Wooley Foundation Fellowships - 1949-50 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 45), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 45 (Reel 19)
  - France - Student Exchange Special Offers for French Students - 1949-54 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 33)
  - France - Marcel De Gallaix Fund for French Students - 1949-56 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 33)
  - France - Cite Universitaire International Congress and Exhibition - The Student Habitat - 1950 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 17)
  - France - Annual Letter - July 30th - 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 19)
  - France - Re Seagram Fellowship - 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 46), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 46 (Reel 19)
  - France - Student Exchange - U.S. Announcements - Publicity 1950-57 (Reel 29, Side 1, Index 42), Reel 29, Side 1, Index 42 (Reel 29)
  - France - Student Exchange Educational Institutions in U.S. Correspondence Re Candidates - 1950, 1953 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 29)
  - France - Re American Lecteurs - 1950-52 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 29)
  - France - American Teaching Assistants Information, Correspondence - 1951-57 (Reel 29, Side 1, Index 41), Reel 29, Side 1, Index 41 (Reel 29)
  - France - Assistantship Program Correspondence - 1951-57 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 38), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 38 (Reel 30)
  - France - Selection Committee Correspondence - Wooley Scholarships - 1952-57 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 29)
  - France - French Normal School Evaluaton - 1953 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 33)
  - France - French Normal School Evaluaton - Laura Barney File - 1954 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 33)
  - France - Fondation Des Etats - Unis Wooley Scholarship Correspondence - 1954-57 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 29)
  - France - Office National Teaching Assistants - Correspondence - 1954-57 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 29)
  - France - Comite D'Accueil French Government Fellowships Correspondence - 1955-57 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 29)
  - France - Office National No. 1 Correspondence - 1955-56 - 1955 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 29)
  - France - Office National No. 2 Correspondence - 1955-56 - 1955 - with Summary Report - 1956 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 29)
  - France - Office National Des Universites et Ecoles Francaises Corrspondence - 1956-57-1956 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 33)
  - France - Department of State (IES) Correspondence - 1956-57 - 1956 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 33)
  - France - U.S. Educational Commission for France Correspondence - 1956-57 - 1956 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 33)
  - France - Miscellaneous Correspondence - 1956-57 - 1956 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 33)
  - France - French Student Reports - 1956-57 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 33)
  - France - Student Exchange French Student Reports from U.S. Colleges and Universities - 1957-58 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 29)
  - France - Student Exchange French Problem Cases - 1956-57 - 1957-58 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 33)
  - France - Office National Correspondence - 1958-59 - 1958 (Reel 29, Side 10, Index 10), Reel 29, Side 10, Index 10 (Reel 29)
  - France - Selection Committee U.S. Educational Commission in France - Correspondence - 1958 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 29)
  - France - Department of State (IES) Correspondence - 1958-59 - 1958 (Reel 29, Side HF.2, Index 16), Reel 29, Side HF.2, Index 16 (Reel 29)
  - France - American Embassy - Paris Correspondence - 1958-59 - 1958 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 29)
  - France - Student Exchange Internal IIE Correspondence - 1958-59 - 1958 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 29)
  - France - Student Exchange French Student Problem Cases -1958-59 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 29)
  - General - Fullbright Travel Grant Procedures - 1949 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 16)
  - Fullbright - Reports - Charles S. Johnson Visits to W. Europe and Egypt - 1952 (Reel 27, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 27, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 27)
  - U.S. Fullbright - Supplementary Young Leaders and Professors Project Correspondene - 1952 (Reel 27, Side 1, Index 21), Reel 27, Side 1, Index 21 (Reel 27)
  - Fullbright - Supplementary Young Teachers and Professors Project Reports - 1952-53 (Reel 27, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 27, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 27)
  - Fullbright - Supplementary Young Teachers and Professors Project Participantts - List - 1953 (Reel 27, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 27, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 27)
  - Fullbright - Board of Foreign Scholarships Meetings - 1952-53 (Reel 27, Side 1, Index 24), Reel 27, Side 1, Index 24 (Reel 27)
  - Fullbright - Austria Student Panel - 1952-53 (Reel 30, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 30, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 30)
  - Fullbright - Australia Student Panel - 1952-53 (Reel 30, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 30, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 30)
  - Fullbright - Burma Student Panel - 1952-53 (Reel 30, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 30, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 30)
  - Fullbright - Denmark Student Panel - 1952-53 (Reel 30, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 30, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 30)